Contact

mdrew@ccf.org

www.linkedin.com/in/mattdrew-43286ab2 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Healthcare

Registered Nurses

Nursing

Languages

English

Matt Drew

Nurse Director at Cleveland Clinic

Cleveland/Akron, Ohio Area

Summary

14 Years in Healthcare

2002 - 2004 Nursing Assistant - Cleveland Clinic

2004 - 2009 Registered Nurse - Hillcrest Hospital

2008 - 2011 Nursing Operations Manager - Hillcrest Hospital

2011 - 2016 Nurse Manager - Hillcrest Hospital

2016 - present - Director Acute Care Nursing - Euclid Hospital

Experience

Euclid Hospital Director of Acute Care Nursing May 2016 - Present (4 years 3 months) Euclid, Ohio

Hillcrest Hospital Nurse Manager April 2011 - May 2016 (5 years 2 months) Mayfield Heights, Ohio

Hillcrest Hospital

7 years

Nursing Operations Manager 2008 - 2011 (3 years)

Mayfield Heights, Ohio

Registered Nurse 2004 - 2009 (5 years) Mayfield Heights, Ohio

Cleveland Clinic **Nursing Assistant** 2002 - 2004 (2 years) Cleveland, Ohio

Education

Indiana Wesleyan University

Master's Degree, Masters of Science in Management with specialization in Healthcare Administration \cdot (2011 - 2013)

Indiana Wesleyan University

Bachelor's Degree, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2008 - 2009)

Lakeland Community College

Associate's Degree, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2001 - 2004)